http://www.bali-beads.com/privacy_policy

Sterling Silver Bali Beads and Jewelry Findings Wholesale
Shopping Cart
0 item(s) - $0.00
Welcome visitor you can login or create an account.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site.
This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information.
The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. Collection of Information We may collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Distribution of Information We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: sales@bali-beads.com
Kind Regards,
